{
    "id": "7e4a7f60a2f64ac696d552a377361d86",
    "title": "Past Simple And Past Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When I ................................. to work, I .............................. Peter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drove, saw",
                "was driving, saw",
                "drove, was seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0bcb89d6c4c44e58381cb7fb1410246"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I ........................................ a bath, the telephone ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was having, rang",
                "had, was ringing",
                "was having, was ringing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed67d723de24422f8a539ea8b3bea533"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ when someone knocked on the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was sleeping",
                "slept",
                "am sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a72fafb22d7e4e17ba06033aa2f071d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "While she ...................................... games, I .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was playing, was working",
                "played, worked",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b60edfeffebe489893ea59925fd46201"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I ............................... my eyes, I ................................... a strange sight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "opened, saw",
                "was opening, was seeing",
                "was opening, saw"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ba89be44da447399600ba59bb3f9354"
        },
        {
            "question": "James ..................................... the lounge while I .............................. supper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tidied, cooked",
                "was tidying, cooked",
                "tidied, was cooking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68676f53c2134c78b17d211ff0eada28"
        },
        {
            "question": "While they ....................................... caroms somebody ........................................ into the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were playing, broke",
                "played, broke",
                "were playing, was breaking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43e66761683746a390bbf2d9953da737"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... of it just when you ..................................... your mouth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thought, opened",
                "was thinking, were opening",
                "thought, were opening"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67ab3e9b9671470c9a32ec073485043f"
        },
        {
            "question": "When she ......................................... a bath, the child ................................. to cry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was having, began",
                "had, was beginning",
                "was having, was beginning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efbbaebc641241e1818a71b2e5b7586f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She took out her pen and .......................................... writing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "started",
                "was starting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94d84e73a9d847099409de7ae65fca2e"
        }
    ]
}